[music]
Hey guys and welcome to this vlog.  This
is another weekend vlog.
Therefore, it's Saturday.  My alarm clock is
going off.  It's really, really warm.  It's
already 26°C, it's 10 o'clock
and I'm going to do my hair now.   I'm definitely going to
Cologne now.  I'm going to visit Julia,
and I'm going to vlog today and
tomorrow about what we do.  Julas, my
plan is actually to get an Assa Bowl
and go shopping, because I really feel like
spending some money right now.  Then
she redoes my nails.
She's also supposed to cut my hair, but
she doesn't know about that yet.  And in the evening
we'll get ready because
we're going to the Bad Bunny concert in
Düsseldorf.  I'll be at
a birthday party later, but you'll
see all that.  But I have
the feeling I'm getting heatstroke or
something.  So, accordingly, I'll remain
without makeup for now.  I've already
packed all my things.  I think
I have an incredibly cool outfit.
I bought it specifically for that purpose.
I think it will get a little
warm because it's a pair of shorts made
of denim and a long, tight
denim jacket.  And I think the jacket will
kill me a little, but whatever.  That's definitely where I am right now
.
And I have another package that
I need to leave at Mila's door.  And now I'm going to
take this bag again, and
I just quickly
painted my toenails because I want to
wear Philip Flops.  I'm afraid it's
not dry yet.
I should have left already.  Well, this
is my
outfit now.
Ah, I still need to put on my bracelets
.  Wait, my top is
from Hollister.  The trousers are by
Stradivarius.
The flip-flops are from Havianas
and the bag is from Coach.  I have
no idea if it's fake or
not.  I got them for my
birthday at some point because I thought they were super
cool.  From eBay or something.
Therefore, I have no idea.  Oh, I'm sweating buckets right now
.  Oh, my
bracelets.  [ __ ].  I don't know if
I'm using all the bracelets right now,
[snorting] because somehow it's too
much for me at the moment.  It's kind of disgusting.
Maybe I'll leave the clock out.  I
think that so often.  In the end, I always put
all the bracelets on anyway.
Therefore, it doesn't really make
sense.  Look, this looks so
incomplete.  No, I have to
get dressed [snort].  I think
I'll leave out this fat one and just take this one,
and then I'll remove this one.
Wow, those earrings are amazing.  Okay, see you
in the car.  Wait.  I turned off
the air conditioning especially for you
so you could hear me.  Anyway,
I've just
dropped my things off at Mila's
and now I'm continuing my journey.  I'm so
hot.  I just stepped outside for
a second.  I'm sweating again.
I don't know what we're thinking,
going shopping now, but my
God, what's with the
sun?  Yes, that's really all I have to
say right now.  I'm
really looking forward to these ace-somethings.  I think it's supposed to be really
awesome.  Well, she looks
beautiful, at least.  I'm really looking forward to
my nails.  I ca
n't explain it right now.  I can tell you,
you'll see how they turn out later anyway,
but I plan to be a bit
cooler.  I simply decided to do it,
and that's why I want to do my
nails like this.  First, back to square,
so not square, ballerina.  I think
many people don't like that, but I kind of like it
.  And then he
checks out this crocodile pattern as a French pattern,
though.  And then with such a dark
green, a kimono.   Some of you might be
realizing it now, some
might not, but you'll see later.
That goes really well with my
outfit, because my outfit for later is
also green.  Yes, this will be amazing.
I'm definitely leaving now,
and yes, I'll see you there.  Hey, dude, my
flight is seriously cancelled.
That's just incredibly awesome.
That makes absolutely no sense.
Is it really painted?
Yes, he's no longer there.
Yes, but they can't
just take another one from you.  Maybe
you'd like to fly a day later
.  Wait, where is that thing now?   Straight ahead
.  Oh, I see. I'm
shocked.  Yes, I really need to
briefly tell you what went down.
Yes,
we've been on our feet for three hours already
, you could say that on our legs
.
Um, actually I wanted to go fat shopping, but it didn't
work out so well.  I
bought two rings.  I'll show you in a moment
.  Yes,
and Asaiball was delicious, blah blah.  And
now we're going to get a Machi.
Diger, the sign was no longer
visible.
Simi,
can I stir this all the way through now?  Dude,
I'm... Oh my God, I'm
overstimulated right now.  No way,
dude, practical, right?  H, I already
sent that to you.
Yes I know.  You didn't order it,
but you could just
drop it in there.  No, I haven't
ordered it yet, because you have my camera.
Jana sent me a tripod and
I thought I'd order it, but
then I realized I do
n't even own that camera anymore.
I swear, I'll buy them
sometime.  I don't really need them
.  That's okay.
Oh, very delicious.
But it's very practical.
Yes,
I want the camera back.  Fun.
Mhm.   That's
delicious.   Yes
.   Uh
.  That's happening
automatically now.
No, I was just there, that was a
huge shock, because it's normally disgusting.
Yes, I'm telling you, it tastes good to me, it always
tastes good to me, actually
never to me.  Okay.  I think that's
absolutely fantastic.  Oh, the buildings are very
beautiful from the outside.   Do
you want to try it?   It
's orange juice with matcha, it
just tastes like oranges, a
little bit like matcha.  Which is crazy, because
it's so incredibly green.
Yes, but it basically just tastes like
Orange Ping.
Yes, but only because he's so persistent
.  Okay, let's go home now
.  Yes,
we are a bit pressed for time,
at least in my opinion.  Jul is
really relaxed.
I'm not relaxed at all.
Yes, it will be fine.
What about the bread now?
Yes, we'll take a look at that right away.
Yes, how about the same?  I thought we were going
home now.
Yes, I would say we go
home first, do all those
things, and then on the way to Barum
train station
I'll pick up Begüm and you can go to
Mhlbergstadt to get Mond.   Okay
.  Or I could ask Mom if it's really that
important.  Yes, I can
also bring bread on the way if I come on Sunday, yes,
then I can bring what
she wants.  Out of.  Oh
, that's the way.
[laughter]
What am I supposed to say now?  Yes, well, we
have time, we have to leave in 2 hours 15
, because it starts... you did
n't even have to enter my address
somehow.
Are you simply without?
No, no, no, no, no.  I have.
Wasn't she there?  OK.  Wang, yeah, what,
man, where was I?
Right, please.
And what was I going to say?  Yes, our
time is up.  We still have 2 left,
already 15. We still have to do my nails
.  I was just about to say, "I'm going to dye my hair
."  Haircut and we're
done.  Yes, I'm feeling a bit clouded
[laughter]
and I mean
I can't talk right now.
Oh, right, get ready.  You know, putting on makeup
and stuff, right?
Dude, I still have to pack my whole suitcase
because I'm suddenly
flying at 0:20 instead of 6 am.
Yes, that's great too.
Huh?  I think that's totally sick.
They can't do that there.   It
's very tasty.  B gave a good
recommendation.   Yes
.  Okay, BG,
we'll start doing my nails now
.  F her.
[music][singing]
[music]
[singing]
[music] Okay guys
, we're done.  Julia is
finished.  This is now the devotion.
Julia is simply amazing.  Awesome.  I just
went down here for a moment because
I have my basket with
all my clothes [music] and my
makeup.  We're late to Lowy, but
whatever.  I will now also wear silver jewelry
.  I specifically
chose that bag because it has silver
on it.  Diger the music, because on this
set [music] here there are only silver buttons
on it and I actually mix, but this
triggers me anyway.  I'll put this on
now.  Okay, I've turned it on now.
I've plastered myself with silver jewelry,
and this is what I look like now.  Where
can I put this?  So, the
boots are obviously still missing, but
[music]
this is the outfit, I think it's
really cool.  Just check out the cute stuff
.  I'll also put on
these black cowboy boots.  And now
I'm going to put on my makeup.   Look
.  Wow, awesome.  Looks really cool.  Who
is Zara?  That's awesome, dude
.
I'm ready now.
Oh, [snorting] Julia is just going to
cut my hair a little shorter in the front and I wanted to
quickly show you my rings.  I initially
copied him a little, but then I found
him
incredibly nice.  I'm not putting them on yet
because I need several and I
only have these two with me right now.  That's
it.  How did the packing go?
Phenomenal.
Full of beauty.   Oh
wow.
Yes,
not that I'm
serious, but nothing more comes out
.
Still uncertain, but it's on its way.
Can you fill up my Stay?   Can
you recognize the sounds?
I don't know, but they're really
slow.
We actually have the most stressful time of our
lives, but we have to
find priorities.  We are hungry.  What's up?  My
God, it's triggering me so much right now
that I couldn't even use TikTok anymore
, huh?
My outfit is so cool.
Is this my Happy Meal now?
No.   Are
you taking the coupon?   Yes
.
Loki.  Actually, it's really stupid that
I'm not using the coupon too, isn't it?   Yes
.
Okay, I'll take one too.
Thanks.
Hey guys, a lot has happened since
our McDonald's visit.  Have you already
mentioned that it starts an hour earlier
?  I don't know.  We thought it would start
an hour earlier because we were
stupid, because we let ourselves be fooled
by some TikToks.
Apparently not.  Therefore, they
have now rushed things unnecessarily.
Actually, we're perfect.
The preview starts in 4 minutes, but we do
n't care about that anyway.  And now we're looking for
the lodge
and
I can't take it anymore.  We're in.  I
can not anymore.  We are not doing well.
It hasn't even started yet, and
not everyone is even inside.  It
's incredibly warm,
but it's huge.
Yes, we're looking for a
cooler place now, if there is one.
We have arrived at a better place:
the food.   Did
you notice that there are cheese rolls?
Cheese baguette.
Yes, I've never seen that before.
That's so cool.  I want
one, and I'd like a pretzel thing.
Okay, let's do it then.  I'll get him
with cheese.  You don't like it anyway?   Yes
.  No, with sesame seeds.   It
's up there.   Yes
.  Yes.  OK.  Ses.  Yes,
I've already touched it.
I still sweat about that.  Should I
cut it open for you?
Uh, no.
Would you like some
cream cheese?
No.  Nothing at all.  That's not really
my thing [music].  Test button.  Bread.
Test button.  By the way, that's also
important.   A
bit sticky.
I was expecting something different,
but this is absolutely delicious.  K the
own
pink
with butter.   That
's delicious.  Is the butter salty?   Do
n't believe it.   Is
nobody sitting there?  [music]
[music]
My ears.   She's
also so depressed.  Julia and
I have to
leave the concert early because of Julia's flight.  I
wanted to fly at 6 a.m.  Yes,
but it's kind of a
review.
It was totally awesome.  I think it was
really intense there.  I wasn't really that hyped, to be
honest.   But then
I was like that, so
I thought it was... I think I'm shouting
right.  Where do we need to go?
You weren't like that.  I wasn't
so sick before, because I'm not sick now either
, so I'm not a
huge world-wide sick person.
Yes, but because I
had no idea or expectation,
I found it all the more shocking.
It was really, really intense
.
The first hour was absolutely awful,
because
it was just so incredibly hot.  I thought
I was going to die
because the roof was closed.   Yes
.  And right now we're having a really
pleasant time.
It was really pleasant.
Yes, it was totally awesome.
It was also cool that it was closed beforehand,
because it was already dark and now it's
light again,
creating two different moods,
but the atmosphere there was crazy.
Yes,
I think I've never been
to a concert where the atmosphere
was so intense.
It was just different because
everyone was
dancing.  I thought that was really
cute.  I have no idea.  I don't
think so, somehow.  I thought that was kind of
cute.  In between I
sounded out and then I
looked at the crowd and everyone was
dancing.  Reall ysweet.  Everyone was so
happy, simply
because of him.  I just
said that to you too.  What did I
say?  That I find that so shocking.   Imagine if
everyone had
so much fun just because of you, only you as the only person.  It's really fun, everyone is
laughing and dancing.  Oh, that's great!  He
must feel amazing.  I can't even see
my car.
Me neither.  We definitely
parked on the left.  Yes, just a very
short way to the right.
I need to change my trousers now.   Do
you think I can just do this quickly here in the corner
?
That's awesome.  Peace, guys.  As you
can see, it's the next day.  It
's dark here, oh God.  It's
10:44 AM.  I don't know what's wrong
with me.  Actually, I was always a very
late sleeper, at least until 12 o'clock.
But I've been awake since 10 o'clock.  And
guys, I have such cool pictures.  I
just finished my Instagram post
and story, and is it okay to be way too
bright sometimes? Is it okay to just
be that cool?
Amazing, somehow.  And guys, my Inst,
I'm so proud of him.  I saw
something on TikTok or something similar
for ideas for Instagram posts,
and it said you should just
take pictures with a
digital camera for a whole day, and then you can put them in the
caption.
And guys, if you don't
tell me this is cool, I'm going to be
incredibly angry, because first of all, how beautiful
is this picture?  I'm very proud of the
picture, and if you have
n't seen it on Instagram yet, well, I'll just show it to
you now.  Wow,
wow, wow.  I
think it's really cool
too.  The picture is kind of
awesome.  But I like them all.  Oh, it's so
cool.  I'm incredibly proud of it.  As
you can see, I put a lot of
thought into my Instagram post, but I just really
enjoy it.  Yes, okay.   Was there
anything else I wanted to do?  I
also have a lot of really cool pictures, I was
at the birthday party yesterday,
but I can't
show them now because there are people in them who
might not get it.  The
birthday party was fun too.  The
last thing I filmed was, I think,
in the parking garage, where I changed my pants
because I didn't want to go there
in boots, and guys, I was
sweating
like a pig.  Omg, but I think
we've already told that story.  It was so
bad.  For some reason,
my makeup was still somehow there at the birthday party
.  I touched up my makeup a little
, but
not really.  It was still there somehow.
I don't know what's wrong with my face either
.  Somehow my makeup stays on
my face well, even though I don't
use setting spray.  That's kind of
crazy.  Ah, [ __ ], I forgot one story
.  Oh well, it was crap anyway.
Um, yes, exactly.  I really don't have
anything more to say right now.  I'm going
downstairs now to chat with my
parents for a bit.  I definitely need to
edit my vlog, which went online last week, because
I edited it one evening
when I had school until 11:30 pm or
so.  I could have slept and
then finished editing it the next day around noon
.  Honestly,
I was at the last stop, I was completely
finished.  I was just about to
import, everything's gone and I
've searched everywhere.  I
called Julia.  I was like, please help me,
I can't do that again, but
it's just gone.  That's why I have to
completely recut it now.  I
think I filmed for five days
.  I've cut it now
.  I'll probably
need another two hours, but yes.  My
God, so he's not coming at 11
o'clock, but he is coming.  Okay,
so it's not that bad.
Otherwise, maybe I'll go to Phx.   Let's
see what else the day
brings.  So guys, as you can see,
I'm wearing a bikini top.  My
vlog is finished editing, it's
currently at 79%
and I'm going to go to the
WHLpool now.  Unfortunately, we have
n't set up our large pool yet, but
I'm totally fine with that.  I'll
also take the whirlpool, of course.  I
just applied
sunscreen.  Diger, what do I look like?
And with this marigold.  Everyone who
saw my last blog post will understand what
I mean.  Apparently, this is supposed to be
great for sunbathing.  No idea
.
Oops.  Okay guys, this is my setup,
my water, my phone.  Here's the
WB, I think...
Oh, no, totally pleasant.  H, my mom
said it was too warm.  I actually think it's
perfect.  The sun is
okay right now, but it's coming out again
.  It was a bit
shady just now, but yeah, I'll chill
for an hour and then
see how long I end up lying here
, okay?  I have no idea how
long I've been sitting here.  It's definitely
2:18 pm and I've just
made myself a small fruit plate and some 90% dark chocolate.  And
now I'm going to chill some more.  I've been
in the pool the whole time.  Now I'm lying down
on the lounger and yes, I'm going to
raise the backrest now.  Okay, I'll sit down now
.  Hey, I'm feeling really
good right now.
[music]
Alright guys, next meal time
.  I've just
whipped up some lunch.  It's kind of like a
Greek bowl.  I'm kind of bothered right now
that
I haven't made any zucchini,
nor have I steamed them.  That would have been absolutely awesome
, but whatever.  Yeah, what can
I say, right?  I'm still lying
here.  I'm going to eat this now.  It's
3:25 pm
and I don't think I'll go to
Fitx anymore, because ugh, no, I'm so
oiled and moisturized.  I have to take a
shower soon and then, well, I don't really have anything
else planned, but
I'd actually like to manage another 5000 steps
.  I've actually been doing
really well lately.
Well, I never usually walk 5000 steps,
but sometimes I have
phases like that.  Wait, do you see?
Sometimes I have this, so the green line represents 5000
steps.  I also have
days like that sometimes, obviously, but
I also have good days sometimes.  Do you see?  The
last few days have been good.  And if I manage to do
5000 more times today
, then I'm in a good position again
, because right now it's still red.
It should at least be orange.  So
at least 2500 steps should be
possible.  Guys, I can't take it anymore
.  I've showered, as you can
see.  I'm currently
wearing a moisturizing mask.  I'm taking them off
now.  Can you hear my fan?  Yes,
because I would
n't survive up here anyway.  I definitely need to
bake a cake because we have
volleyball at school tomorrow and I
signed up to bake a cake,
and I still need to bake my muffins
for breakfast, but
I can't do that right now because I'm dying from the
heat.  It's a little better downstairs,
but still not good, so I need to
cool down a bit longer.  Until then
I'll just chill, because no,
I can't do more.  I'm taking care of that now.  It
wasn't even that cooling, because it did
n't feel cool at all.  That's why
I would really like to know where
my soap dispenser is.  Huh?  Who stole my
soap dispenser?  Am I being
stupid right now?  Where is it?
Understood.  My soap spinner is gone.
Gil.  Huh?  Someone stole it from me.   Doesn't matter.
I would definitely say so.
Oh, I see. That's why I'd really love
a
skincare breakfast
fridge. What am I rambling on about?  A skincare refrigerator,
because it's so cool to be able to really
cool your face in the morning during the summer
and put masks in there too.
But somehow too stingy.  I think I
even
received one once.  I have no idea if I
still have it.  That was a really long time ago
.  But maybe I'm just being
stupid.  Okay, this needs to settle in for a bit.
I'm spraying my ear piercings again
, but I'm not using the
medical earrings
because, no, I'm not in the mood for that anymore.  They are a
little inflamed.  Well, a
little bit of age does show sometimes, but
not that much.  It's a bit red,
but oh well.  Hey guys, where's my
soap?
Wow!  No, this can't be real.
She loves it.  Am I stupid,
actually?  Wow.  Oh my God, that was
incredibly stupid.  We'll all forget that right now
.  It's the warmest place here in the bathroom,
and that's the
worst part,
because when I put my cream and stuff on here,
I sweat and
then I'm just rubbing the cream in with my sweat, and
ugh, it's not nice at all.  By the way, did
I ever talk about my new serum
?  It smells like sausage water, which is
really abnormal.  Julia had that
too, well, not anymore, because this
is hers.  She just gave it to me
.  One of mine is already
empty because she says she can't
use it because it stinks so much, and it does
, but somehow I don't care
anymore.  So for the first few days I was like, oh my god
.  But Mom said I do
n't smell like sausage water.  That's why
it's really only like that for the first 5
minutes when you apply it.  But
then it goes away and somehow it does
n't bother me anymore when I put it on
.  It's not great, but my
God, beauty is pain, right?
I saw on TikTok
that it's supposed to be the best Vitamin C serum on the
market, which I ca
n't really imagine because it costs
€10.
How can this be the best option?  But yes,
I think it's good.  I still occasionally use
the one
from No Cosmetics.
I used to use that all the time,
but it's so oily, so it just stays on the surface, it does
n't absorb.  So your skin
is oily all day.  If you touch it
, you'll get an oily film on your
finger.  That's why sometimes, for example,
if I know I'm going to wash my hair the
next day, I
sometimes leave it on overnight, because it
also gets into your hair and then it gets
oily.  Yes, but I still use it
sometimes because I somehow
feel that it
's still good.  So, I'm like this
.  I still like it, though.   Do
you get it?  Because that makes the skin
so soft.  No idea.  Ugh,
I'm starting to be protective again.  I
need to go to the fan for a moment.  Okay, that did
n't really help much.  I'm going to put on some
sunscreen now.  It's already
5 pm, but this is the
first time I've done my skincare today
, so this is basically my morning stuff that
I'm applying right now.
Oh right.  Yes, because I still
want to reach my step goal, right?   That
means I actually
need to go out again, and for that I obviously need...
Okay, I can feel the sweat
coming on.  Therefore, I'm now sprinting
to the fan.  It is exactly 6:30 PM.
I was kind of half asleep
.  I've finally gotten myself together
and I'm going to
make my banana muffins for breakfast, and
people, not the
marble cake I'm making for school.  I really don't feel like it
, but whatever.  Let's go.
[singing]
[music]
So guys, my muffins are ready.  They are
standing here and the cake needs
about another 14 minutes.  But last time it
took much, much longer.   I have
no idea.  And I've just
prepared my dinner.  I think I
overdid it a bit with the amount, but I
made myself some buckwheat noodles with DM pesto and zucchini, and
now I'm going to lie on the sofa and
watch Sarah Begani's new vlog.
Come on, I'm so hot, but
thank God I have a fan here again
.  I've just pointed it directly
at myself.  That is very
nice.  Yes, I'm going to eat now.  Peace
guys, it's the next day.  It's
Monday.  Therefore, I will
end this vlog here.  I didn't
film anything after baking yesterday
because there was nothing left for Locky either.  I didn't do anything particularly
exciting,
and I hope you enjoyed watching me spend
my weekend
.  I thought it was absolutely
amazing.  I'm getting ready
for school right now.  I had my first loot
free.  I'm incredibly hot right now.
The.  What?  It's only 22°C.
It feels like 35. Before I
hang up, just one more thing.  I've got
Lipstein on right now, and this
thing here.  And somehow I find it
really beautiful right now, so I'll show
you what I used.
Namely this one in Everyone's Nude
Pink by Essence Line and Stain.  You
always have to be a little careful
while applying it and
blending it right away, because otherwise
[snort] it's just such a thick
line.  But if you manage to do that
, it's cute.  I really like my outfit
today.  My top is
from Hollister.  I don't think that exists anymore
.  And the trousers are from
Berschka, they're currently in style.  I'm definitely going
downstairs now to cut
my cake, which I made for today
.  And yes, I hope you
enjoyed the vlog.  See you next week.
Peace out.